Guide to the Russell Van Nest Black papers, 1919-1968.
Black, Russell Van Nest papers
- Series IX. Drawings, Maps and Plans
  - New Jersey and New York
    - Lawrence, New Jersey, Cornell # D-136 (Box 54)
    - Livingston, New Jersey, Cornell # D-132 (Box 54)
    - Mercer County, New Jersey - Preliminary, General, and Planting Plans, Cornell # none (Folder 2)
    - Millville, New Jersey, Cornell # D-37 (Box 52)
    - Moorestown, New Jersey, Cornell # D-36 (Box 57)
    - Moorestown, New Jersey, Cornell # D-111 (Box 61)
    - Morrisville, New Jersey, Cornell # D-135 (Box 55)
    - Mount Olive, New Jersey, Cornell # D-130 (Box 52)
    - New Brunswick, New Jersey - Map, Cornell # none, 1954 (Folder 2)
    - New Brunswick, New Jersey, Cornell # D-117 (Box 57)
    - New Jersey State, Cornell # D-147 (Box 72)
    - New Jersey State, Cornell # D-148 (Box 72)
    - Passaic County, New Jersey, Cornell # D-24 (Box 53)
    - Passaic, New Jersey, Cornell # D-19 (Box 67)
    - Peddie School, New Jersey - Kalomathia House (listed as being in Hightstown, PA), Cornell # none, 1929 (Folder 2)
    - Peddie School, New Jersey, Cornell # D-119 (Box 60)
    - Plainsboro, New Jersey, Cornell # D-122 (Box 71)
    - Plainsfield, New Jersey - Map, Cornell # none, 1955 (Folder 2)
    - Princeton Nurseries - Map (listed as being in Kingston, New Jersey), Cornell # none (Folder 2)
    - Princeton Nurseries, Cornell # D-131 (Box 52)
    - Princeton, New Jersey - Route 206 By-Pass Map, Cornell # none (Folder 2)
    - Princeton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-11 (Box 51)
    - Princeton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-107 (Box 52)
    - Princeton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-134 (Box 57)
    - Princeton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-129 (Box 60)
    - Princeton, New Jersey - Topographical and Streets, Cornell # D-16 (Box 69)
    - Princeton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-2 (Box 71)
    - Princeton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-145 (Box 72)
    - Princeton University, Princeton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-25 (Box 52)
    - Rockefeller Institute (listed as being in Plainsboro, New Jersey), Cornell # none (Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Institute - Planting Plan, Cornell # D-113 (Box 56)
    - Rocky Hill Park, New Jersey, Cornell # D-48 (Box 71)
    - Round Valley, New Jersey, Cornell # D-125 (Box 51)
    - Sea Isle City, New Jersey, Cornell # D-13 (Box 71)
    - Somerset, New Jersey - County Map, Cornell # none, c. 1936 (Folder 2)
    - Somerset, New Jersey - Park Plan, Cornell # D-6 (Box 60)
    - South Orange, New Jersey, Cornell # D-15 (Box 53)
    - Trenton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-108 (Box 52)
    - Trenton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-106 (Box 58)
    - Trenton, New Jersey, Cornell # D-52 (Box 69)
    - Watchung, New Jersey - New Jersey Topographical Map, Cornell # D-12 (Box 63)
    - Wayne, New Jersey, Cornell # D-110 (Box 57)
    - Hyde Park, New York, Cornell # D-64 (Box 56)
    - Ithaca, New York - Proposed Planting Plans, Cornell # D-29, 1925 (Box 60)
    - Monticello, New York, Cornell # D-51 (Box 60)
    - Monticello, New York, Cornell # D-53; D-54 (Box 65)
    - Newton Falls, New York - Paper Mill, Cornell # D-26 (Box 65)
    - Syracuse, New York - Plans for the Mrs. Francis Nye Reisdence, Cornell # Plans by F.W. Field, 1925 (Box 72)
    - Syracuse, New York - Stephens Building, Cornell # none (Box 72)
  - Pennsylvania
    - Adelphia, Pennsylvania - Evergreen Farm, Cornell # D-109 (Box 56)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania - Future Land Use, Cornell # D-43 (Box 51)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-115 (Box 52)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-103, 1945 (Box 53)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-114 (Box 54)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-10; D-22; D-41 (Box 61)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-100 (Box 62)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-80; D-89 (Box 64)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania - Aerial Photo, Cornell # D-21 (Box 65)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania - Urban Renewal Study - Dwelling Occupancy, Cornell # D-45 (Folder 3)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania - Urban Renewal, Cornell # D-45 (Box 67)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-40; D-42, 1945 (Box 70)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania - Trexler Estate, Plans for "Springwood Farms", Cornell # none (Folder 3)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania - Trexler Estate, Cornell # D-95 (Box 51)
    - Allentown, Pennsylvania - Trexler Estate, Cornell # D-68 (Box 69)
    - Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-78 (Box 66)
    - Bethlehem, Pennsylvania - Site Plan, Cornell # D-27, 1941 (Box 68)
    - Bethlehem, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-44 (Box 70)
    - Bethlehem, Pennsylvania - Housing, Cornell # D-39 (Box 71)
    - Bristol, Pennsylvania - Mill Creek Park, Cornell # D-85 (Box 68)
    - Buckingham, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-74 (Box 71)
    - Bucks County, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-17; D-84 (Box 68)
    - Central Berks Region, Cornell # D-46 (Box 56)
    - Cleona, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-38 (Box 51)
    - Delaware County, Pennsylvania - Smith Property, Cornell # D-112 (Box 54)
    - Doylestown, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-93 (Box 60)
    - Emmaus, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-83 (Box 54)
    - Emmaus, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-102 (Box 62)
    - Emmaus, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-98 (Box 63)
    - Emmaus, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-69 (Box 68)
    - Lancaster County, Pennsylvania - Zoning Maps, Cornell # D-23 (Box 55)
    - Lancaster, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-86 (Box 58)
    - Lancaster County, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-8 (Box 67)
    - Lehigh, Pennsylvania - Tax Maps (Salisbury), Cornell # none (Folder 3)
    - Lehigh, Pennsylvania - Tax Maps, Cornell # D-20 (Box 64)
    - Lower Paxton, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-82 (Box 52)
    - Lower Wakefield, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-99 (Box 56)
    - Lower Wakefield, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-144 (Box 65)
    - Manor Township, Pennsylvania - Road Map, Cornell # none, 1933 (Folder 3)
    - Manheim, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-96 (Box 53)
    - Millersville, Pennsylvania - Proposed Borough, Cornell # none (Folder 3)
    - Mount Joy, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-18 (Box 71)
    - Mount Vernon Plan, Cornell # D-30 (Box 54)
    - New Hope, Pennsylvania - Ricker Estate Garden Plans, Cornell # none (Folder 3)
    - New Hope, Pennsylvania - Ricker Estate Garden Plans, Cornell # D-58 (Box 64)
    - New Hope, Pennsylvania - New Hope Community School, Cornell # none, 1945 (Folder 3)
    - New Hope, Pennsylvania - Solebury Bank Parking Lot, Cornell # none (Folder 3)
    - New Hope, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-88 (Box 73)
    - Ontelaunee Township, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-104 (Box 60)
    - Ontelaunee Township, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-140 (Box 61)
    - Ontelaunee Township, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-81 (Box 62)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-3 (Box 54)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Regional Plan, Cornell # D-141 (Box 59)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania - Tri-State, Cornell # D-5 (Box 65)
    - Salisbury, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-92 (Box 63)
    - Salisbury, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-105 (Box 68)
    - Salisbury, Pennsylvania - Aerial Photo, Cornell # D-67 (Box 69)
    - Schuykill Haven, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-79 (Box 57)
    - Schuykill Haven, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-73 (Box 60)
    - Schuykill Haven, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-9 (Box 66)
    - Schuykill Haven, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-97 (Box 66)
    - Schuykill Haven, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-101 (Box 68)
    - Solebury Township, Pennsylvania - Robert Taploy Property, Cornell # none (Folder 3)
    - Solebury, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-118 (Box 58)
    - South Whitehall, Pennsylvania - Zoning and General Plans, Cornell # none (Folder 3)
    - South Whitehall, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-76 (Box 58)
    - South Whitehall, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-72 (Box 60)
    - South Whitehall, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-90 (Box 61)
    - Wilson Borough, Pennsylvania - Meuser Park, Cornell # none, 1943 (Folder 3)
    - Wilson Borough, Pennsylvania - Meuser Park, Cornell # D-91 (Box 68)
    - Yardley, Pennsylvania, Cornell # D-94 (Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous or Unknown Location
    - D'Arclay Estate, Cornell # D-73 (Box 51)
    - Jersey Homesteads, Cornell # D-87 (Box 52)
    - New Jersey City on Delaware River, Cornell # D-142 (Box 54)
    - Augenblick Estate Garden Plan, Cornell # D-57 (Box 69)
    - Typical Street Cross Section, Cornell # D-65 (Box 70)
    - Augenblick Estate Planting Plan, Cornell # D-1 (Box 71)
    - Black's Christmas Trees, Cornell # none (Folder 4)
    - Diagrams for Planning for a Small City, Cornell # none (Folder 4)
    - Lamington and North Branch Reservoir, Cornell # none (Folder 4)
    - Studies for Lancaster Avenue and Wynnewood Avenue Intersection, Cornell # none (Folder 4)
    - United States Population Distribution Urban and Rural, Cornell # none, 1960 (Folder 4)
    - United States True Raised Relief Map, Cornell # none (Folder 4)
    - Walter Hayes School - Planting Plan, Cornell # none (Folder 4)